corwin.com 2015-11-17

# Corwin: Privacy Policy

Corwin Press, Inc. (“Corwin”), a subsidiary of SAGE Publications, Inc. (“SAGE”) values our relationship with you and recognizes the importance of protecting the privacy of your personal information. This Privacy Policy explains how we may use your personal information. If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy or your personal information, we can be contacted via mail, email, or phone at the following:

### 

2455 Teller Road  
Thousand Oaks, CA 91320  
E-mail: info@corwin.com  
Telephone: 800-233-9936

For more efficient and expedient handling of your request, please include exact name, contact information, and, if possible, account number(s).

### 

For each visitor to our Web Site, our Web server automatically recognizes and collects only your domain name, but not the e-mail address, unless you volunteer it. Corwin uses standard cookie technology, which you can disable through your Web Browser Options, to store visitor's preferences, record session information, such as items that consumers add to their shopping cart, and record past activity at a site. We do not use cookie technology to harvest email addresses or other personal information. Additionally, when you view our Web Site by linking from another web page we may store the name of that web page. All the information collected through cookies is for internal use only and is used to compile aggregate information to analyze site, page, and service usage and consumer purchasing behavior. Our goal is to provide you with the best possible experience on our Web Site. For more information on cookies and how Corwin uses them, please visit [www.sagepub.com/cookies.sp](http://www.sagepub.com/cookies.sp).

### 

Some areas and content on our Web Site may require you to register with us or log-in in order to access such areas and/or content. 

### 

As part of the registration or account setup, Corwin may require your email address. The email address you provide as part of the process will be used to contact you or otherwise process your transaction. 

### 

As part of purchasing products from Corwin, requesting services, participating in surveys, or accessing special areas on our Web Site, you may be required to supply us with personally identifiable information (“PII”).  

Corwin may use your PII for internal purposes, to process your transaction, or for marketing purposes. 

Since some areas on our Web Site are co-branded with or sponsored by a third party, you should be aware that your PII may be shared with such third parties and we encourage you to review their separate privacy policies. 

Corwin does not respond to “Do Not Track” signals or other mechanisms that provide consumers the ability to exercise choice regarding the collection of PII about an individual consumer’s online activities over time and across third party web sites or online services. Corwin does not track such online activities. 

Corwin may provide access to course materials and/or services to educational institutions, associations and other similar customers through its web site or through a third party web site. Information collected on these web sites is only used by Corwin and such customers and third parties as needed in relation to the course materials or services which may include, without limitation, the collection and tracking of certain usage data. Student records which may include PII may be protected by the Family and Educational Rights Privacy Act (FERPA).  

You should be aware that if you voluntarily disclose your PII (such as your name or email address) in a forum accessible to others (e.g., on blogs, bulletin boards, chat areas and other similar forums including, without limitation, those hosted within a social site), your PII may be collected and disclosed by others. Corwin cannot take responsibility for such collection and disclosure. 

We may also disclose PII in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this PII is reasonably necessary to: comply with the law, enforce or apply our terms of business, protect our rights and those of our users, or with your consent. 

If you do not wish to have your PII exchanged or disclosed, please see our contact information above.

### 

We do not partner with or have special relationships with any ad server companies.

### 

We understand that the security of your PII is important. Corwin uses industry-standard encryption technologies when transferring and receiving consumer data exchanged with our Web Site. However, despite our efforts, no encryption technology is completely secure and Corwin cannot ensure or warrant the security of your PII. Therefore, any transmission of PII is at your own risk.

### **Cross Border Transfers**

Your PII may be transferred across national borders including, without limitation, to our other offices located in the U.K., Australia, India, and Singapore. ****

### **Access to Personally Identifiable Information**

If you have provided us with your PII, you may be able to view and update your PII by logging on to the Corwin site and reviewing and/or modifying the information contained in your account or profile. To request that we make any changes to your PII, please email your request to marketingservices@sagepub.com.

### **Other Questions**

If you have any questions or concerns about how we have handled your PII, you can email us at [marketingservices@sagepub.com](mailto:marketingservices@sagepub.com). We will respond to such questions and concerns within a reasonable period of time.

### 

This Corwin Privacy Policy is subject to change at any time. We encourage you to review this Privacy Policy regularly for any changes.

Revised 06/15
